MITCH: Here we are in beautiful Ibiza, Spain.
Beautiful sand.
Beautiful waves.
My favorite shorts.
And my favorite girl who is about to get...
Oh, my God!
Hey!
- Come on, give it to me.
- MITCH: No! Stop! Come on!
- Mitch!
- MITCH: This is great!
I'm serious.
MITCH: Oh. Oh, my God. That is so cute.
Honey, this is like... (CHUCKLES)
Let me film for just a couple minutes.
- It's like we're honeymooners.
- Oh, my God!
MITCH: ♪ Honeymooners ♪
- "Honeymoon"?
- MITCH: Yeah.
We're not married.
Katrina Harper...
You're my best friend in the whole world.
Oh, my God. Babe, stop it.
You're gonna make me...
If you get emotional, you're gonna kill me.
I'm trying to get through this, babe.
I love you, more than anything.
Will you marry me?
Oh, my God! (CHUCKLES)
- Yes!
- Yeah?
Yes, Mitch Rapp.
I'll marry you.
Sorry, it's hard one-handed.
You like it? It was my mom's ring.
I love it.
I love you.
- I'm still...
- Are you filming? Oh, my God! (LAUGHING)
Yeah, I'm still recording.
I'm trying to get this.
Come on, Mitch!
This is why I was filming now.
You see, now you get it.
Smile.
I'm gonna get drinks.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Don't be too long.
I won't, I won't.
I love you.
- (GIGGLES)
- I'll be back.
Engagement drinks in the water, people.
- WOMAN: Whoo-hoo!
- (PEOPLE APPLAUDING)
Oh. Thank you. Thank you.
Very sweet, thanks.
Babe, we're getting applause.
I love you.
Thank you.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Hola. Como estas?
What can I get you?
Um, can I just get two drinks, please?
Dos bebidas, if that's right...
Um, I just got engaged, so something special.
It can be anything, though.
Oh, you lucky guy.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
Oh, can they be kinda strong too?
Is that cool?
(BARTENDER SPEAKING SPANISH)
Thank you, man.
Oh, whoa. Maybe not that strong.
(GUNFIRE)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Katrina!
(GROANING)
Katrina?
Katrina!
Mitch!
(GROANS)
(FIRES GUN)
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
MANSUR RECRUIT: We're gonna fucking
set your shit on fire, man!
Fuckin' burn, motherfucker, burn!
AL-MANSUR:
To our brothers across the globe...
Come join our fight against
American imperialism.
They will pay for the murder of our families,
our friends, and all children.
(WOMAN SHOUTING IN ARABIC)
SOLDIER: Hold it, hold it, hold it.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
All right, stop! Come on, man!
INSTRUCTOR: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let him go, let him go.
Let him go, let him go!
Break it up. Let him go!
OPPONENT: What the fuck is your deal, man?
That's it. You're done, Rapp. Get out.
OPPONENT: He keeps doing this shit.
Get out!
MITCH: Have a nice fucking day.
INSTRUCTOR: You were out of line.
Back to work. Keep moving.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(FIRES GUN)
- (MAN SHOUTS)
- (ALARM RINGING)
MAN: Get outta there!
You're gonna get yourself killed,
you dumb-ass!
MAN 2: What's up with this guy?
MITCH: Fuck!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Rapp, why I gotta tell you again?
Sorry, Mr. Nazir.
I didn't realize it was past 10:00.
I'll try to keep it down.
Yeah, enough with the sports.
Copy that. All right. Thanks, Mr. Nazir.
BEN: He's up again.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(CONVERSING IN ARABIC)
Assalam-alaikum.
Walaikum-assalam.
(BOTH SPEAKING ARABIC)
(GRUNTS)
Why have you come?
To help Adnan al-Mansur
achieve his people's destiny.
Inshallah.
I wanted to look in your eyes.
I don't trust you.
I'm prepared to die a martyr.
What can I do to earn your trust?
(GUNSHOT)
(MEN COUGHING)
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
No!
SOLDIER: Step away, now!
(GRUNTING)
Come on!
The fuck off me!
(GRUNTING)
He's dead, it's over.
Easy. Easy. Take it easy.
Area's secure.
DR. FRAIN: You wanted to kill them all,
and then go on killing.
Pretty extreme, don't you think?
No, I don't think that's extreme at all.
I think people like that deserve to die
in the worst ways you can imagine.
What do you remember
about your parents' death?
Car crash.
I was in Massachusetts.
They were in Tunisia at the time.
I was 14.
That's what I remember.
You started having discipline problems.
Got yourself kicked out of
three boarding schools.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
I wonder what that was about.
DR. FRAIN: Let's talk about what happened
after that day on the beach.
MITCH: Oh, Jesus Christ.
Again? Are you kidding me?
DR. FRAIN: (SCOFFS) Yeah, again.
You gave up everything
after that, didn't you?
Your grad studies at Brown University.
- MITCH: I must have lost interest.
- DR. FRAIN: In everything?
MITCH: No, not everything.
(DOOR OPENS)
MITCH: See you later, Dr. Frain.
See you tomorrow, same time?
I like the new look.
Irene Kennedy, CIA Deputy Director
in charge of Counter-terrorism.
I know who you are.
Any idea how long you been here?
30 days.
Enough time for you to figure out
a couple things.
Yeah, yeah. I've figured out
a lot about myself.
It's been a very reflective time. Thank you.
You wouldn't have made it through
the next 20 seconds there alive.
I guess we'll never know now, will we?
You told Dr. Frain you thought
you were gonna kill Mansur
and wipe out his whole cell.
For starters.
Mmm-hmm.
You had an even bigger agenda,
didn't you, Mitch?
What did you think, you were gonna jump
from cell to cell taking out terrorists?
Righting the world's wrongs?
Got to Mansur, didn't I?
I mean, it's more than you accomplished.
I'm gonna let you in on something.
Our people here, they don't know
what to do with you.
A lot of them think we should
just throw you in a supermax.
Me?
I like your agenda, Mitch.
I can help you with it,
if you throw in with us.
We can teach you how to play
with the big boys.
Yeah, let me stop you right there.
You don't think I considered
that 18 months ago?
Joining the CIA?
I made the decision to
pursue Mansur on my own
'cause I knew I could get it done.
What you need to understand
is that I'm the only way.
To get what you want.
Why the hell would I trust you?
Because I believe in you.
And I'm all you've got.
CIA OFFICER: What's been confirmed is
the enriched plutonium has been stolen
from a decommissioned
Russian nuclear facility.
If they get their hands on a nuclear trigger
and a physicist to build it,
they'd be able to arm it
and detonate it at any time.
IRENE: Tom?
He's testing through the roof.
Might be the best I've ever seen.
We've had him under surveillance
for six months.
Martial arts, gun skills.
I've surveilled dozens of these vigilantes.
This one is different.
Yeah, well, I've gone over these, Irene.
He's non-compliant, he's oppositional.
He got us into Mansur's cell.
That's a hell of a lot more
than we ever managed.
All right, Orion is an elite unit, Irene.
A secret unit.
Reports to you, me, and no one else.
I don't want to be responsible
for that kind of mistake.
Now, that's Hurley talking.
Yeah, well, he's called me twice about this.
This kind of psych profile
scares the hell out of him.
As far as he's concerned,
you're sending him a Section 8
with an ax to grind.
What happened to that kid on the beach,
it changed him.
You can't train that into someone.
His psych profile is exactly
what I've been looking for.
(STANSFIELD SIGHS)
Polygraph?
Flying colors.
All right. Good luck with Hurley.
Oh, Irene.
We'll have fresh intel on the Russian
plutonium situation in two hours.
Stay by your phone.
Yeah.
You can take the blindfold off.
So, what do I need to know about this guy?
IRENE: Stan Hurley.
He's a warrior.
Ex-Navy SEAL.
My daddy served with him in the Persian Gulf.
Did you go through this program?
IRENE: I went through a program.
Not this one.
It's not like becoming a spy or Special Ops,
none of those things.
Good.
DR. FRAIN: So, what are your goals, Mitch?
MITCH: My goals?
My goal is to have them lie awake at night,
knowing I'm coming for them.
(DOG BARKING)
I thought you were supposed
to be on the patch.
You saw those tests. Yeah, I saw them.
He's off the charts.
I've seen off the charts before.
And he's got none of the bad habits
he'd have to unlearn
if he had military training.
Unlearn?
Come on, Stan.
You drop one of your Navy SEALs
in an urban setting,
you can spot the boot camp
on them a mile away.
We're not fighting the...
Cold War? Yeah, I know.
You keep telling me that,
Miss Deputy Director.
Oh, wow. "Miss Deputy Director."
Your daddy would agree with me.
I'll be checking in with you every 48 hours.
I'm on a plane to London in the morning.
And go back on the patch, for God's sake.
Don't prove me wrong.
(ENGINE STARTING)
She ain't coming back.
Hey.
Eyes front and center.
Sorry.
"Sorry"? Do I look like one of
your college professors?
You talk to me, you call me "sir," son.
Yes, sir.
What the fuck you doing here?
Did you have some bad things happen to you,
some shitty things happen to you?
Now you wanna kill those mean old terrorists.
Go get some bad guys.
What makes you think you can make it
through my selection process?
Permission to speak, sir?
Sure, go ahead if you got something to say.
Like this is all a big mistake
and you wanna go home.
You wanna go home? Good.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'll drive you myself.
Not at all, sir.
I was gonna suggest we maybe
speed this whole thing up?
My guess is, if you and I go hand-to-hand,
you could probably figure out
inside of 20 seconds
whether or not I have what it takes to
make it through your selection process.
So, what do you think?
We got an empty cot, empty footlocker.
They're both yours as long as you can last.
Sounds good.
Follow me.
See you out there.
Heard a lot about you, by the way.
Excited to see what you got.
Kill me.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
People think you can slice
a man's throat like this.
That's only in the movies.
Right there.
Do it.
No noise. No mess.
(MITCH PANTING)
Victor, you're up.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
What the fuck, man?
Who grabs a fucking blade?
Come on, you fuckin' pussy. Let's go!
You gotta have eyes in the back of your head.
You flinch, you die.
Orion is about the mission.
It ain't about you.
You go down out there, you're a ghost,
you don't exist.
There's nobody, nobody coming back for you.
You're about to be captured.
(GUN CLICKS)
Bye-bye.
(SPITS)
STANSFIELD:
We now know 15 kilos of plutonium-239
went missing during the Russian breach.
IRENE: It's enough to build
a full-scale nuclear weapon.
But that would likely require
the resources of a nation-state.
As Iranian Chief of General Staff,
I share your concern.
We have been monitoring
the situation as you have.
I'm afraid we too are in the dark.
ASHANI: For Iran, of course,
a nuclear weapon is off the table.
We have a treaty.
You have countrymen who are
not too happy about that.
We monitor your nuclear enrichment
program pretty closely,
but black market plutonium-239 from Russia...
Would be difficult for inspectors to detect.
Ms. Kennedy, yes?
- (BEHRUZ CHUCKLES)
- Mmm-hmm.
I assure you as Minister of Defense
that we in Iran recognize
how much the spirit of comity
between our nations would be compromised
if we were to acquire
weapons-grade plutonium from any source.
STANSFIELD: Yes, it would.
Same goes for your clients outside Iran,
Hezbollah. Hamas.
The Houthis.
Nuclear weapons are a danger
in any hands, Director.
Wasn't that your pretext for your invasion
of our neighbor to the west?
One that cost 500,000 Iraqi lives
and left a wake of destruction
from which our region has never recovered.
General Rostami, we came only
to tell you what we know.
(BEHRUZ CHUCKLES DRYLY)
Is that a threat?
Of course not, Minister Behruz.
Gentlemen, I very much
appreciate you meeting with us.
ROSTAMI: Not at all.
I only wish we could offer more insight.
Thank you.
STANSFIELD: I don't trust General Rostami.
We need to keep this quiet.
How ready is Orion?
I'll check in with Hurley.
(GUNSHOT)
INSTRUCTOR: Why is there no one on watch?
(GUNFIRE)
You're all dead.
VICTOR: Yeah, yeah. I got it, I got it.
You're dead.
What?
You wanna say something to me?
Say it. Go on, say it.
You got 30 seconds!
HURLEY: These are your targets.
Memorize them.
It's your responsibility
to be able to identify them.
You shoot a combatant, you get a point.
You miss, you get a shock.
You shoot a noncombatant,
you get a bigger shock.
Combatant shoots you...
Let's just say you're gonna feel it.
Ready?
Go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GROANS)
What's Hurley doing?
He's fucking with his head.
(GUNSHOTS)
(BOTH GROAN)
(GROANS)
Fuck!
Fucking AR bullshit.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Shall we?
Okay.
That's clever.
Raw plutonium.
Highly enriched, as promised.
Let's hope.
(CRACKLING)
Wow, that's a beautiful sound, gentlemen.
May I?
(EXHALES) Okay.
Wire the money.
That, I can do.
This is a cell phone.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(GHOST SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKING POLISH)
GHOST: Okay.
(SPEAKS POLISH)
(ALL SPEAKING POLISH)
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
NEWS ANCHOR: It now appears that all seven
victims were shot with a single weapon,
believed to be a Glock 29.
Traces of weaponized plutonium
were detected inside the van
where the bodies of three Russians
and two Warsaw police officers were found.
The Russian government has confirmed
that the chemical footprint
of the plutonium in question
is a match to the plutonium that was stolen
from the decommissioned
processing facility in Tobolsk.
Security footage is being
analyzed by Polish police,
now working in conjunction with Interpol,
to identify the shooter and his connection
to the missing plutonium.
The identity of the shooter
remains unknown...
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Hi, excuse me.
How can I help you? Question.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
CASHIER: May I help you?
MITCH: No, thanks. I'm okay.
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
- HURLEY: Hey! Hey! Hey!
Rapp! God damn it!
You have to stay under control.
WOMAN: Dickhead!
Asshole doesn't know when to quit.
- You're kidding me, right?
- I just saved your ass.
You've gotta know when the mission's
been accomplished, Rapp.
- Sir, he's a fucking...
- Which he did.
Never assume your target is the only target.
The enemy dresses like a deer
and he kills like a lion.
And that's what we gotta do.
We just gotta do it better.
All right.
You're an asshole.
(DOOR OPENS)
We got a problem.
Six weeks ago, there was a breach
at a decommissioned
Russian plutonium facility.
I'm aware.
What you don't know is 15 kilos
of plutonium went missing.
Weapons-grade.
That's a shit-ton of plutonium.
And it just changed hands.
I wanna show you something.
Take a look at this.
Does that face bong a gong for you?
Or is it just me?
It can't be him.
Our drones took him out after
the embassy bombing at Bamako.
We never got a positive ID.
That's our mad dog out there.
All right. Let's say it's him.
It's him, Irene.
This gives us a chance to kill
two birds with one stone.
Hamdi Sharif.
He's an arms dealer working out of Turkey.
Four days ago, he purchased
a Russian-designed nuclear trigger.
And he's gonna be selling it.
IRENE: Sharif's got the honey.
Now we just wait for the bee.
We go in, we fuck up their deal.
And we take 'em both out.
You're going to Istanbul.
We have an agent in place.
She'll meet you at the airport.
All right.
Annika Ogden. We've had her
on the ground over there
for five years.
I want Rapp on the team.
Really?
He's ready, Stan.
Actually, Irene, he's not ready.
But he will be.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yeah. Shut the door.
We're shipping out.
Set those down there.
You like movies?
Sure.
MITCH: I got something for you.
What the fuck is this?
Yeah, I thought so.
- You thought so?
- Yeah.
Why are you even alive, Rapp?
You ever asked yourself that?
Why you? You know, of all those people?
You're special, I guess.
KATRINA: Oh, my God!
You want me to turn it up?
- KATRINA: I'll marry you!
- MITCH: Take it!
You're a fucking coward, you know that?
Turn that shit off.
MITCH: What do you think? It's my mom's ring.
You gonna turn it off?
- MITCH ON VIDEO: Katrina!
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (MITCH GROANS)
HURLEY: Am I supposed to feel sorry for you?
I don't.
(GROANS)
(CHOKING)
You made a big mistake.
You let emotion cloud your judgment.
Never, ever let it get personal.
You understand?
(PANTING)
(COUGHING)
(CONTINUES PANTING)
Yeah, I got it.
Be ready to go by 5:00.
See you at 4:30.
You know what you're gonna do here?
- No, sir.
- Correct. You don't.
So keep your eyes open and your mouth shut.
And wait for my orders.
(ALL CONVERSING IN TURKISH)
(ALL GREET IN TURKISH)
Hamdi Sharif, a real-estate
mogul/arms dealer.
He's like Santa Claus for terrorists.
Scumbag.
Spare me your junior-year-abroad
moral opinion, would you, Rapp?
Not really an opinion, sir.
Sharif's a piece of shit.
It's not a crusade.
This mission is practical. Don't make it...
Personal?
- Exactly.
- Yes, sir.
Victor, you're with me.
Rapp, you and Annika are eyes on.
ANNIKA: Sharif has a routine.
Let's see if anything breaks his pattern.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
All right, we got 48 hours.
Quick, clean. No footprint.
This town's ready to blow as it is.
(INAUDIBLE)
ANNIKA: Where the hell are you going?
(SPEAKS TURKISH)
That was fucking reckless, Rapp.
I took the initiative, sir.
- VICTOR: He could've been made.
- Well, I wasn't.
Here we go.
11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
A meeting at a restaurant on Akbiyik Street.
That's right before Sharif
goes to see his mistress.
That breaks his pattern.
VICTOR:
I'll tell you what'll break his pattern.
When that fucking assistant tells his boss
he lost his goddamn phone.
MITCH: He won't.
He's too afraid of Sharif to let him know
he screwed up.
All right. We go tomorrow.
What's the mission, sir?
Eliminate the target.
Eliminate the recipient.
Obtain the package.
MITCH: And what's the package?
We'll know it when we see it.
You're lead.
You're backup.
(SPEAKING TURKISH)
(CONVERSING IN TURKISH)
He thinks we're married.
Don't think too much.
You'll lose your nerve.
No, I don't think so.
It'll be your first time.
Yeah, not in my mind.
Lead, your friend's arriving now.
VICTOR: Copy.
And he brought a shitload
of military protection.
HURLEY: I'll take care of the MPs.
Oh, come on, now, honey. Don't be mad.
No, no, no.
I had a few. Yeah, I did.
I'll make it up to you when I get home.
You know that.
(BOTH SPEAKING TURKISH)
Call it in. Call it in,
or I'll cut your fucking throat.
(SPEAKING TURKISH)
(WHISTLING)
(SOLDIERS CHATTERING IN TURKISH)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(SIREN WAILING)
(CHOKING)
HURLEY: Lead, you're a go.
Survey 2, get in place.
Be careful in there. I got it.
Pardon.
(TURKISH MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHARIF SPEAKING TURKISH)
(GROANS)
- (PEOPLE GASPING)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Target's gone. Target's gone.
Get back!
Lead?
Dead.
Mission terminated.
Exfil to secure location. Confirm.
Survey 2, you better let me
hear you fucking confirm.
God damn it, this is a fucking mess.
We're out of here.
(SPEAKING TURKISH)
(START ENGINE)
(BOTH SPEAKING TURKISH)
Don't worry, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm gonna hurt your boss.
(SPEAKING TURKISH)
(DOGS BARKING)
Shit.
Hurry up!
(SPEAKS TURKISH)
(DOGS SNARLING)
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
(PANTING)
(SPEAKS TURKISH)
(DOGS BARKING)
(SPEAKING TURKISH)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(MITCH GROANS)
(GROANS)
No, please.
Please, don't. Don't.
No.
You disobeyed a direct order.
MITCH: No, I made a decision to pursue
the target, and I completed the mission.
And, sir, isn't that what I'm here to do?
Isn't that my job?
Your fucking job is to do
what I fucking tell you to do!
What, you prefer I leave him alive,
then, let him go? That piece of shit?
(DOOR OPENS)
Stan?
Good, you're here.
I wanna show you something.
Wait here.
Look at that. That's the kind
of bullshit that could shut us down.
Kid can't even follow a fucking order.
Victor got made. Rapp didn't.
Why does this kid give you
such a fucking hard-on?
Don't talk to me like that!
I'm your superior.
My superior, Irene?
Your superior, God damn it.
Do you have any idea how long I spent looking
for someone with that kid's talent and balls?
Rapp stays.
HURLEY: You're giving me an order?
That's an affirmative.
Can you give us a minute?
Look at this.
The trigger must have been in that car.
HURLEY: Look at him.
Lookin' at me.
Everything he did there,
I taught him how to do it.
Stan.
HURLEY: I should've left him in the Navy.
I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
IRENE: Stan, listen to me.
The only thing that matters now is that
fucking lunatic has everything he needs
to build a nuclear weapon.
STAN: He's got a trigger.
Now he needs to buy a physicist.
We just have to figure out
where they're gonna build this thing.
Ben.
That computer our boy Rapp
lifted from Sharif's house,
there's evidence of a $2 million
transfer to a bank account in Rome.
Cash prepped for withdrawal.
Rome.
(MAN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(BOTH SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Your money.
GHOST: I've been reading up, Minister.
You Iranians probably
all learn this growing up,
or at least you did before
you signed that treaty.
But me, I had no idea about these fun facts.
Yeah, I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Inside three miles,
apparently you just vaporize.
Some folks don't.
They get all black and charred,
and dense as lead, and no one knows why.
Inside five miles,
everything is sucked into a void,
hotter than the core of the sun.
How about that?
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
You'll get the rest of your money
when the job's done.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Where is my physicist?
He'll pick up his money,
then we'll pick him up.
(JAVEED SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
We'll need an extra day to configure
the weapon, then it's all yours.
Kill as many Jews as you want.
Do you practice Salah, brother?
I receive my payment, complete the project.
That's my practice, brother.
Very well.
MITCH: Who was that guy?
In Istanbul.
It seemed like he was a step ahead of us.
Hey, you gonna fill me in here or what?
There's some bad people planning
on doing some bad things,
and it's our job to stop them.
You still haven't said anything about Victor.
Victor's gone. Victor doesn't exist.
What is it you think we do here, Rapp?
I think we kill people who need to be killed.
And who do you trust to tell you?
I follow orders.
No, you follow orders when they suit you.
This whole thing is pretty much
just a means to an end for you, isn't it?
A lot's happened in my life, sir.
- Really? Huh.
- Yeah.
So you think you were sent here
as an outlet for your self-pity,
and your anger, and all your guilt. Right?
Patriotism exists
because people like you and people
like me need a higher cause.
Something bigger than us.
That stink coming outta you
you like to call "revenge,"
the rest of us call "shit."
And as soon as it starts to feel good,
that's when you stop being a professional.
And then what are you?
Tell us something good, darling.
We're in their system.
The moment that transfer from
Sharif's account is picked up,
we'll know it.
Boy, you just smile, and the Red Sea parts.
Works in the Med, too.
I'll bet it does.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Cash withdrawal from Sharif's account.
$2 million, U.S.
There's our physicist. Let's go.
Welcome to the Boscolo and enjoy your stay.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
He's in 1448.
And we're next door.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Code in.
Victor-Charlie 1109.
HURLEY: Confirmed.
MITCH: Suite 1448.
We're in 1449, right next door.
All right. We'll grab the physicist,
and we'll take out whosever coming for him.
Signal every 15 minutes.
Hey.
I know what happened to you.
I'm sorry.
I understand you.
More than you know.
I know what it's like
to lose people you love.
We're gonna get these fuckers.
(GROANS)
Fuck!
Where the hell are you?
Hurley...
Where is he?
I don't know what you're talking...
(GRUNTS)
(MITCH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
Where is he?
He outside?
(GRUNTING)
(MAN GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
BARTOSH: Please, no.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Please.
MITCH: Hurley, what the fuck?
I thought you were eyes on,
why didn't you spot 'em?
They were already in the damn hotel.
Local mafia's working with 'em.
I'll tell Kennedy we have the physicist.
What the hell just happened out there, huh?
That's twice now this guy's
blown up our entire op.
What's the target? Huh? What's the target?
- I don't know, mister.
- Yeah, you do.
Huh?
Do you think I'm stupid?
He's an American. He said your name.
Did you train this guy?
- You like to smoke?
- Oh, Jesus Christ!
- Are you a smoker?
- BARTOSH: I don't...
- Wait!
- Bad habit.
Wait, stop! Wait, wait! I know something.
- What do you know?
- I know something.
There is a man... There is
a man they call Ghost.
Ghost. I think it was an Iranian man said it.
Uh-huh. Where are they building the bomb?
- I just took the money.
- Where are they building it?
Where are they building it?
All right, here.
Take some time to think about it.
Ghost. Is that his name?
Why is this guy after you?
Something personal, sir?
They're building a nuke.
Hotel Navona.
- Clean yourself up.
- Wait.
(BARTOSH GRUNTING) Don't go.
NEWS ANCHOR: America's president
has ordered the Sixth Fleet
out of the U.S. Naval base in Naples, Italy.
The Sixth Fleet is now
southwest off the coast...
Let me help you.
No, it's okay. I'm fine.
You're not.
(SIGHS)
How are you holding up?
I was afraid today.
I thought we were going to die.
Yeah, I'm either always afraid
or never afraid.
I don't know which.
There you go.
Just relax now.
We'll search for Ghost tomorrow.
(GASPS) You scared me.
Who are you?
What do you mean?
You said "Ghost."
- What about him?
- I never told you that name.
Hurley did.
Yeah, I think you're full of shit.
- Mitch.
- Who are you?
- Mitch, what's wrong with you?
- Who do you work for?
I'm CIA.
Now don't fucking lie to me!
I'm not lying!
You're Iranian, aren't you?
Get the fuck away from me!
(GROANS)
(CHOKING)
Are you working with the Iranians?
(COUGHING)
Tell me the truth. Tell me the truth!
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
You Iranian intelligence?
Are you Iranian intelligence?
What do you know about Ghost?
CIA OFFICER:
We're gonna need the decryption device.
You were right, Mitch.
This Iranian mole is a tough nut to crack.
All I could get from her
was her handler. Azad Ashani.
Happens to be a friend of mine.
I'm gonna go pay him a visit.
- Okay, I'm going with you.
- No.
I need you to stay here.
Kennedy's on her way with the CIA team
and a Mossad team.
She's gonna ask me where you went.
What the hell am I supposed to say?
That's right, she is.
And you're gonna be smart,
and you're gonna keep your mouth shut,
and you're gonna cover my ass.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I still have it.
(CHUCKLES)
Very nice.
I am always happy to meet you, Stan...
But never happy why.
Well, maybe next time we'll meet for pizza.
Your girl's tough, by the way.
Go easy on her.
She's my niece.
Yeah.
What have you got for me?
The men behind all this are General Rostami,
our military chief of staff,
and our defense minister, Behruz.
Both are very powerful,
and both are very angry about
the nuclear treaty we made with you.
They have been trying to acquire
nuclear materials for the past two years.
And they are the ones
who hired the mercenary called Ghost.
Rostami is now in Tehran,
but Behruz is here in Rome.
Annika has been tracking
his movements through his cell phone.
And they're building it here?
I wish I knew.
We have their physicist.
They can't build it without him.
But...
The mercenary asked Behruz
to use one of ours, an Iranian.
Behruz agreed. That was rash.
It means they are in a hurry.
And the target's Israel?
I wish I had better information for you.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GROANS)
(HURLEY GROANS)
Where the hell is Hurley?
You gotta tell me what's going on here. Now.
That guy he trained, who the hell is he?
That's not something you
need to know right now.
What are you covering up?
When you've got a level-5 security clearance
and 20 years' experience, talk to me.
Until then, shut up and do your job.
I want her cell phone decrypted and scanned.
BEN: Local PD pulled a body
from the harbor an hour ago.
Gunshot to the chest.
Iranian intelligence officer, Azad Ashani.
Christ!
That's the guy Hurley went to meet.
Stupid son of a bitch!
All right, so what do we do?
We gotta go after him.
There's a fucking nuke in play, Rapp.
That's the mission, and the only mission.
This is now a joint CIA-Mossad operation,
whether we like it or not.
Can you get the Director on the phone?
So you're just gonna write him off then?
That's the plan?
Stan Hurley is the closest
thing to family I've got.
And if he were standing here
right now, his only question would be,
why are we wasting our breath
talking about him?
You're through here.
You're going home, that's an order.
Now, sit down and shut up.
Why are you helping me?
Your handler Ashani was killed.
Hurley was with him. Something happened.
I'm going after him.
I need your help.
We gotta go.
GHOST: Stan.
I've looked forward to this.
I'm sure you have, Ronnie.
I wanna show you something.
All right.
Savages. Right, Stan?
But you know something? I don't blame them.
I blame you.
Never would've happened if you
would have followed orders, Ronnie.
"You go down out there, you're a ghost."
"You're a John Doe."
"You get captured?"
Oh, you remember. That's very gratifying.
Thank you.
You made me proud today, Ron.
You should've come for me.
Ten men would've died.
You put 10 men's lives in danger,
'cause you couldn't follow a fucking order.
- Fuck you.
- GHOST: Fuck orders.
- Fuck the mission!
- Fuck you.
This was me. I was your boy, I believe that.
You made me believe that.
Ashani had their people tracking
Minister Behruz's secure cell phone.
MITCH: So, we find Behruz, we find Hurley.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Mitch!
(DRIVER SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(HORNS HONKING)
HURLEY: Oh, yeah, look at that.
Did you learn that in Aleppo?
No.
You always told us what to expect, Stan.
Now, where's the rest of your team?
(LAUGHS) Come on, Ronnie, really?
Don't call me that.
Where's the rest of your team?
Your new boy out there, he on my tail?
Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie.
There's your first mistake.
You never start with a real question.
You start slow.
You get inside your subject's head.
Stan, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
(SIGHS) There's your
second mistake. Number two.
You don't say, "one more time."
You already...
(GROANING) Damn!
(SHUDDERS)
Now, what's that third mistake, Stan?
Huh? What is it?
Go ahead! Go ahead!
I got nine more! I like this.
I like it. Go ahead, bring it on!
You motherfucker!
(MAN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Ronnie wants to know if I got a team outside.
Right, Ron?
If it's safe to move your bomb.
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
Are we being followed?
Where's the new me?
I've done my research. I know all about him.
"The new me..." Oh, you mean Mitch?
You know, Mitch, he's unpredictable.
You never know about Mitch.
He might be here, he might be there.
He's like you, but you're a real Section 8.
Enough.
- Schizo mom.
- Where are they?
- Loser dad.
(GROANING)
God!
Where's the rest of your team?
Half-wit mom, psycho dad...
- You're pond scum.
- Where are they?
Pond scum! You're fucking...
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- (GROANING)
I'm sorry about your handler.
Ashani was my uncle.
I'm sure it was Minister Behruz
and General Rostami who had him killed.
They want nuclear war with Israel.
We tried to stop them.
My brother and father
both died fighting them.
Corviale. Turn here.
You know what my real mistake was?
I trusted you.
You made me feel like
I was the Second Coming.
And you acted like my father.
I trusted you and I trusted
the United States Navy.
(HURLEY GROANING)
U.S. of A. Does it, it's gotta be good.
Right, Stan?
Except
nobody told me the business
y'all are really in.
You create monsters.
That's just what you do.
Those people who did this to me,
you think they're barbarians?
Bullshit.
(GROANING)
Where's the decryption I asked for?
Rapp grabbed her smartphone
before we could get any of it.
And we can't find him.
Surveillance cameras picked up Rapp
taking out our agents five minutes ago.
What the hell are you doing?
There's not a single thing happening here
that you didn't make happen.
God bless fucking America, huh, Stan?
Hoorah!
I can tell you where Mitch is...
GHOST: What's that third mistake, Stan?
Mitch...
I can't hear you.
(GHOST GROANS)
Fuck!
Third mistake,
never get too close.
Finish your personal business here.
Your work is done.
The bomb is armed.
- Timer is set up?
- Yes.
He's playing you.
Bomb's not for you, it's for him.
It was his plan all along!
Dead zone.
We're not getting any signals here.
(MITCH SIGHS)
MITCH: Come on. Come on.
Wait a second.
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
(MEN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
What are you gonna do with it?
GHOST: No, Stan.
"What are we gonna do with it?"
Why are we in Rome, Ronnie?
I like Rome.
It's good food.
Never, ever thought I'd die in the field.
Ain't it crazy?
I always figured it would be, I don't know,
some cabin in the woods with my dog.
GHOST: Me?
I think I want water.
There's just something
peaceful about dying at sea.
All right.
Let's get it over with.
No, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
I ain't gonna kill you.
You're gonna live to see
the crown of your creation, Stan.
Thousands of Americans are gonna burn.
All because of you.
Enjoy the show.
Get ready.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Go.
(MAN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(MAN GRUNTING WEAKLY)
(MAN COUGHING)
BEHRUZ: Please help me.
Annika.
(BOTH SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(YELLS)
Whoa!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GROANS)
CIA OFFICER: We've got an explosion detected.
Here.
A half click off the Fiumicino waterways.
It's underground.
- Delta One, go!
- Let's go.
IRENE: Get a chopper out there.
(HURLEY GRUNTING)
You're not supposed to be here, Rapp.
Yeah, what are you gonna do, fire me?
There's another passage down there.
He's got the nuke.
- You gonna be good?
- Go. Go!
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
GHOST: Put the gun down.
Or she's dead.
I want to see my family, Mitch.
No, Annika, you don't.
I want to see my family.
GHOST: Come on, Mitch. Be nice.
She wants to live.
She wants to see her family.
Put the gun down.
Annika!
(GUN CLICKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
The bomb can't be stopped.
Just like you couldn't stop
that beautiful girl from dying on the beach.
Irene.
The bomb's on a boat.
IRENE: Hurley?
How do you know?
Ronnie wanted to die at sea.
Is the Sixth Fleet out on maneuvers?
IRENE: Oh, my God.
Bring up ISR feeds.
Get me eyes in the sky over the coastline
and put the Sixth Fleet on nuclear alert.
Tom.
The target is the Sixth Fleet
and it's 25 miles offshore.
It's a shame.
The last thing your girl saw
was you not saving her.
(LAUGHS)
MAN ON P.A.: General quarters.
All hands, man your stations.
This is not a drill.
I repeat, this is not a drill.
Inbound, small vessel-borne nuclear device.
Man decon stations.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Didn't Hurley teach you
anything, little brother?
To never make it personal.
(YELLS)
This isn't personal.
(GROANS)
(COUGHING)
Shit.
The bomb has a timer and a release trigger.
We take out his boat, it'll detonate.
If it goes off above the waterline...
Disaster. There'll be fallout
all over the mainland.
USS Flynn...
Prepare to engage.
The boat is turning, sir.
Who's driving that boat?
Rapp.
Go.
Sir? Go!
What are you doing? Hurley.
Hurley?
HURLEY: Trying to get our boy
to throw the bomb in the water.
Flynn, you are clear to fire when ready.
Do not fire, Commander. The boat is turning.
CAPTAIN: If we don't engage,
that guarantees detonation.
I understand there's a risk,
but this is the best chance we've got.
Shit! God damn it!
There he is.
Get me on that boat's marine bandwidth.
Rapp!
Can you hear me? Pick up the radio!
Throw the bomb overboard!
No way, sir, I gotta get
further away from the fleet!
Rapp!
For once in your life, take a goddamn order!
The Sixth Fleet is about to blow you to hell!
HURLEY: Command, Delta Two,
the bomb's in the water.
Commander, hold your fire!
The bomb's in the water.
Flynn, hold fire!
Hold fire!
Got less than 30 seconds.
All right, go! Get outta here!
Jesus.
(MEN SHOUTING)
CAPTAIN: Brace for impact.
Sir, yes, sir!
Holy shit.
Hold on!
(ALARM BLARING)
Brace!
You shouldn't have come for me.
Don't get used to it, son.
(LAUGHS)
Hurley...
Looks like we're gonna be all right up here.
I think.
Damage control central. Report.
OFFICER: Pressure is normalizing.
We have multiple hull breaches.
Radiologicals, Eisenhower?
Low... Low levels.
Initiating countermeasure wash-down.
Commander, any casualties?
The Flynn took some serious damage.
The casualty reports aren't in yet,
but if it had gone off above
the waterline, I don't think we'd be here.
Eisenhower,
my prayers are with you all.
Hurley, is Rapp there?
Hold on a minute.
Yeah, go ahead.
You okay, Mitch?
Oh, yeah. I'm fantastic.
You saved a lot of lives today.
Took some losses, too.
What the hell are you looking at?
You look like a mummy. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
Well...
A mummy doesn't have to write up reports.
Dictate them. You should be good at that.
NEWS ANCHOR:
Iranian official, General Rostami,
the leader of the minority
opposition in Tehran,
claims that he has proof that a secret group
of assassins within America's CIA
are responsible for
last week's nuclear event.
With the Iranian presidential election
just two weeks away,
General Rostami continues
to rise in popularity.
They say General Rostami is
gonna be the next President of Iran.
Yeah.
He didn't even have to blow
up Israel to get there.
He's gonna be a major pain in the ass, too.
Where's Rapp? I can't reach him.
How the hell do I know where Rapp is?
I'm a mummy in a hospital.
Rostami has full support for restarting
Iran's nuclear program.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)